(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-26T13:10:01.677279",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
yo yo yo...
we are ねぽらぼ and...
We are Nepolabo and...
we are holoX
watcha
gatcha!
check it out!
3, 2, 1, go!
ねぽっくす!
Nepolabo!
watcha gatcha, whatcha gonna do? yeah!
ねぽっくす!
Nepolabo!
watcha gatcha, whatcha gonna do? yeah!
clap your hands everybody
ラッパッパー crazy party
Rap-appappa, crazy party
退屈を蹴飛ばして
Let's blow away our boredom
本気で遊ぼうぜ
And play with all our hearts
バリバリ上げましょう度数
Let's turn the volume all the way up
爆ラブ混ぜればドキスン
Mix in some wild love for a thrill
ガオガオ獲物をlock on
Lock on to our target, gao gao!
ジャッキン!!ジャッキン!!のっと切り抜け
Jackpot! Jackpot! Slice right through it
ショータイムの始まりだ
It's the start of the showtime
騒え (yeah!!)
Get wild (yeah!)
叫べ (yeah!!)
Shout out (yeah!)
楽しんだもん勝ち
Whoever has fun wins in the end
つまらない世界はもうぶち壊せ!!!!
A boring world is meant to be shattered!
(are you ready?)
メチャクチャにしちゃえストーリー (watcha gatcha!!!!!!!!)
Let's make this story a total mess (Watcha gatcha!)
予想できないくらいがいいじゃん
It's great when it's totally unpredictable
ガンガンいこうぜ
Let's charge ahead full speed
ぶっ飛べ!
And blow it away!
ゴチャ混ぜにしていこうぜ (watcha gatcha!!!!!!!!)
Let's make it a chaotic mix (Watcha gatcha!)
かなりヤバめのコラボレーション
A pretty wild collaboration
ノイズ混じりの熱狂(wow!!)
A frenzy mixed with noise (Wow!)
この“瞬間”を感じて
Feeling this "moment"
だって なんだっけって てぇてぇ
Saying "what is this?" and "tehe!"
“今”が“未来”の“本物”
Today is the "real deal" of tomorrow
(watcha gatcha!!!!!!!!)
ねぽっくす!
Nepolabo!
watcha gatcha, whatcha gonna do? yeah!
ねぽっくす!
Nepolabo!
watcha gatcha, whatcha gonna do? yeah!
こんばんは！
Good evening!
ほら！せっかくさ、君はあんなにアイドル衣装がどうのとか昨日配信してたのにさ、これだよもう。
Look! You streamed yesterday about how great your idol outfit was, and now look at this!
あ、でもね、本当にあるね、そのほら、お披露目のあのサイン書くやつ。すごくない？
Ah, but it really is there, look, the one where you write your signature at the reveal. Isn't that amazing?
画面に書いてたんでしょ？とてもね、ねね、ねねがね、自分にあの、都合のいい向きで書いたからね、みんなには逆向きで見えちゃった
It was written on the screen, right? Nene wrote it facing the way that was convenient for her, so everyone saw it backwards!
結構さ、今日何やるかってさ、お互い言わなかったじゃん？
We didn't tell each other what we were doing today, did we?
あ、だからさ、さっきね
Ah, so earlier...
え、でもいっぱいつっこんじゃった。え、でもそれはそれで
Eh, but we made so many comically timed jokes. Well, even so...
なんか、味があるじゃん？味がある。まあね、お互いのをかぶったり、まあよかった。
It has a certain charm, right? A charm. Well, matching each other or whatever, it was good.
いいなと思った。なんかすごい演出が斬新だった。
I thought it was nice. The staging was really original.
そうね。初めてみたことながらね。
That's right. While seeing it for the first time.
いや、揃ったね。
Man, we matched.
揃った。揃った！
We matched. We really matched!
ね、あと、お前らの俺らを最初にさ、あのね、あの、倒れて…
Hey, also, first you guys fell down...
あ、そうか、そうそう、あれ、ファンのタタ…そうね、ファンの…
Ah, right, right, that, fan ta-ta... right, fan...
ファンタジー小説。ファンタジーのナレーションやってる人かと思った。ゲーム始まっちゃうよ。
A fantasy novel. I thought you were a fantasy narrator. I thought a game was starting!
目覚めたらアイドルだったね。
When you wake up, you're an idol.
目覚めたらここわステージっていうのね。
And then you realize, "Ah, this is the stage."
いやアイドルだから、ドクリング聞こえなかったわ。
Well, since we're idols, we couldn't hear the heartbeat sound effect.
でもお前らVTuberだからドクリング聞こえないっしょ、笑っちゃうよね。聞こえないね。
But you guys are VTubers so you wouldn't hear heartbeats, right? That's funny. You can't hear them.
え、そっか。何？
Eh, is that so? What?
え、じゃないんだわ。え、何これ？
Eh, no it isn't. Eh, what is this?
ラミーがさ、なんか着替えしたのめちゃくちゃさ綺麗だったねターンが。
Lamy, your outfit change and the turn you did were super pretty!
キューッていう。また画像技術が使われてた。
That "shwoop" sound. They used image tech again.
いや後ろのピンク本当可愛いな。
Man, the pink in the back is really cute.
かわいい、見て、後ろ見て。みんな後ろ向いてほら。
Cute, look, look at the back. Everyone turn around, look.
え、ポルカとねねの、あ、ポルカとラミのが逆になってるのね。そう、いらって。
Eh, Polka and Nene's... ah, Polka and Lamy's are reversed. Yeah, mirrored.
そう、左右対称になってるの。そうだよ。
Right, they're symmetrical. Exactly.
ちょっともっと引きで撮ってください。
Please take the shot from a bit further back.
みんな自分でそれをやるのがめっちゃ面白いよ。
Doing that all by yourselves is hilarious.
いや、今日みんなテンポ高いな。高い、そうでしょう。そうだよ。
Man, everyone's tempo is high today. High? Of course. That's right.
高いです。褒めすいな。で、あと最後のCのいいよ。
It's high. Praise us! And finally, that C note was great.
よかったな。最高だったよね。
That was good. It was the best, right?
もうちょっと、なんかね。
A bit more, you know...
でも、クーキー、あのクーキーだよね。あのマーシュマロウがなんかに入れたクーキー、ちゃんと。
But, Cookie, that Cookie, right? The marshmallow cookies that Marshmallow put in, properly...
ちゃんと作りましたみたいな、ちゃんと自分で作りました。
Like, "I made them properly," made them by herself.
いや本当になごんだ。なごんだ、よかった。
Man, it was really heartwarming. Heartwarming, good.
え、SRV、まさか焼かれるとは思わなかった。爆破してんのにさらに焼かれるんだっていう。
Eh, SRV, I never thought I'd get burned. We're exploding, and on top of that, getting burned!
でさ、100万人記念ね。おめでとう、あったじゃん。
And then, the 1-million subscriber milestone. Congrats, that happened.
あれね、全然知らなかったから、そうなんですよ。
I had no idea about that, so yeah.
え、超いいじゃんと思った。よかったぜひ後でチェックしてください。
Eh, I thought it was super nice. I'm glad, please check it out later.
はーい！
Yay!
さあ、どうする？え、じゃあ何をするどうするの？
Now, what should we do? Eh, then what are we gonna do?
見てみて、ねねさ、オレンジかと。ピンクなんだよ。
Look, look, Nene, you think it's orange, but it's actually pink!
あ、やっぱ、ピンクのほうがいるね、足。足。
Ah, as expected, pink is there, legs. Legs.
あ、みんな足。足、ほら、いつも。
Ah, everyone's legs. Legs, look, as usual.
いいよね、それ。
That's nice, right?
私はトランプ柄。ねねはももの花と、もも。
Mine is a playing card pattern. Nene's is peach flowers and peaches.
いいね。みんな結構ほら、みんならしい、違うんだよ。だって、服によってこっちにつけてるのも違うよね、確か。
Nice. Everyone is quite, you know, true to themselves, it's different. Even the side where it's attached on the outfit is different, right?
私こっち。ラミーちゃんどうしようかな。あ、そうそう、ラミーといっしょ。
Me on this side. What about Lamy? Ah, right, right, same as Lamy.
ええ、そうなんだ。おお、本当だ。ね、うちらふたりだもん。いっしょでしょ？
Eh, is that so? Oh, really. Hey, there's just the two of us. We're the same, right?
え、そこ、太もものそこだけついてるのやばいな。
Eh, having it only right there on the thigh is crazy!
やばいな。今日は特にまとめて。ほら、ほら、ほら、何、何、何。
It's crazy. Today especially, all together. Look, look, look, what, what, what.
これ、見ていいよ。え、何、何？
You can look at this. Eh, what, what?
え、なんか違うんだよ。なんだろう、次元が違うような、ロデオしてるような。
Eh, it feels different. Like a different dimension, or like riding a rodeo.
それはちょっと違うだろ、それは。
That's a bit different, come on.
腕に通じてるのもいいな、ししろん。
Shishiron, having it attached to your arm is nice too.
腕の先取りもみんなついてる。いっしょじゃないかな？
Everyone has it on the fingertips too. Isn't it the same?
ああ、でね、耳がね、あれなんだよね。リボンがね、めちゃくちゃかわいい。
Ah, and also, the ears are like that. The ribbon is super cute.
そうよ。あ、耳。え、耳？ともい。そう、ぷくぷく、ぷくぷくだけどさ、このリボンがいいやな。
That's right. Ah, ears. Eh, ears? Tomoi. Yeah, puffy, but this ribbon is nice.
そう、ネックレスにほんと、いいね。
Right, really goes well with the necklace.
ああ、かわいい。あ、ていうかさ、なんか、
Ah, cute. Ah, I mean, like...
そうやって見ると、ししろん本当ロリーだな、やっぱり。
Looking at it that way, Shishiron is really loli-like after all.
うそやん。結構ね、なんかTwitterとか見てても。
No way. Even looking at Twitter and stuff...
そうロリーっていう、いつもほら、かっこいいからさ衣装が。
Like "so loli," because your outfit is usually so cool.
だから、今日このアイドル衣装を着た感じ、どんな感じになるのかすごい楽しみにしてるリスナーさんいっぱいたけど。
So, I was really looking forward to seeing what it'd be like when you wore this idol outfit today.
みんなどうだったかな？
I wonder how everyone liked it?
感想またちょっとね、ねぽらぼアイドル衣装で、
Impressions again, please check out the Nepolabo idol outfit...
あれしてほしい。なんか、もう集中切れちゃった？
Please do that. Wait, did you lose concentration?
集中切れちゃったかな？
Did you lose focus?
みんなちょっと、みんな今日ちょっと落ち着かないね。だって嬉しいんだもん。
Everyone's a bit unsettled today. Because we're so happy!
切れってさ。やめなさい！
Stop it. Cut it out!
やめなさい、やめなさい！
Stop it, stop it!
じゃあ、ちょっと…
Well then, let's...
ねぇ撮影とかしようか？ 撮影会する？
Hey, shall we do a photo shoot? Want a photo session?
え、なんか撮りたい人とかおる？
Is there anyone you want to take photos of?
え、ねぇ、もっとたい、もっとたい、ほんと。下からリアな。
Hey, take more, take more, really. From below, right?
じゃ、ねねがカメラ持って、みんなのこと撮ってみましょうか。
Then, Nene will hold the camera and take pictures of everyone!
よん。どんな風に撮ってくれるの？
Four. How are you going to take them?
コメント欄もなんか拾ってみよっかな、なんかあったら。
Let's also pick up some chat comments if there are any.
なんかあったら、どんなのがいい？
If any, what kind is good?
え、でもみんなかわいしかなくない？
Wait, aren't you all just super cute?
へそ！うわっ！やめてまじ。ねねぽるの。
Navel! Whoa! Stop it, seriously. Nene and Polka's!
え、待って待って、お腹かわいいね。
Wait, wait, your stomach is so cute.
おへそが充実かよ。ししがみカード。
Such a well-fed navel. Lion-god card.
あ、これです。え、これ、ししがみのポーズ？
Ah, this is it. Eh, is this the lion-god pose?
あ、いいね、この、横？
Ah, nice, this... sideways?
もうちょっと、あ、ラミィちゃんももうちょっとこちら。もうちょっとお尻プリンって突き出して。
A bit more... Lamy-chan, a bit more this way.
Stick your butt out a bit more.
え、ちょっとお前ちょっとカメラもうちょっと頑張れよ。
Hey, you, camera, try a bit harder!
ダメ出しされてんじゃねえか。おいちょっと、ねぇねぇ、どうですか？ガ、ガ、ガ、そうそうそうそう！もっと下からでもいいよ。いいねいいね、最高！
You're getting criticized! Hey, how is it?
Yeah, yeah! From even lower is fine. Awesome!
よし。なんか、厄介オタクみたい。
Alright. Kind of like a troublesome otaku.
ちがう違う、それ以上アイドルライクを燃えないでって話。
No, no, I mean don't extinguish
the idol-like vibe beyond that.
アイドルライクなんかないからさ。え、これすごい楽しいじゃん、なんだこれ。
Because there's no idol-like vibe.
Wow, this is so fun, what is this?
おまるも、はい、おまるもずっといて。え、なんか来る？おまるの真ん中？
Omaru too, yes, Omaru stay there too.
Eh, something coming? Omaru's center?
はい、まんなか。ぽるかさんのしよう、ぽるかさんのする？
Yes, the center. Let's do Polka-san's,
shall we do Polka-san's?
ぽるかさんのする？あー…おまるんは、ちょっと厚みが…おや、おや、おや？
Shall we do Polka's? Ah... Omarun
has some thickness... wait, wait, wait?
おまるんは、ちょっと、厚みがない。
Omarun doesn't have much thickness.
何の厚みなんだよ！どんな感じ？「おしりさいこう」
What kind of thickness is that!
What kind of feel? "Butt is the best."
こう、お返しをとおし！お返しをとおし！いいよ、その、困ってる感じのポーズ！
Like, give it back! Give it back!
Good, that troubled pose!
困ってる感じのポーズ！困ってるぽるかいいよ！
The troubled pose! Troubled Polka is good!
お返しをとおし！何で使ってんの、どうしたの？
Give it back! Why are you using that,
what happened?
どうしたの大丈夫？いや急に、どうしようおかしいよ！
What happened, are you okay? No, suddenly,
what should I do, it's so weird!
バグっちゃった。じゃあ次、次の人、次の人は、誰も、誰も…
It bugged out. Okay next, next person,
next person, nobody, nobody...
あ、もうそうか？あ、いいよ、じゃあ、ラミィもそうか。
Ah, is that so? Ah, okay,
then Lamy too.
じゃあ、どんなのがいい？
Then, what kind is good?
じゃあねねぽるでなんかやる？ねねぽる？はい。なにな、なんこれ？
Then shall we do something with Nene & Polka?
Nene & Polka? Yes. What's this?
なにこれ、なになにこれのやつかな。え、背中合わせとかどう？背中合わせいいじゃん！同じ！
What is this, is this that one?
Eh, how about back-to-back? Great!
ああ、かわいい、かわいい！かわいい、どう？いいね、すごい、あ、あ、あ…
Ah, cute, cute! Cute, how's that?
Nice, amazing, ah, ah, ah...
いいね、いいね、いいね！これ、横にしたらめっちゃ世界が爆笑になる！
Good, good, good!
If you turn this sideways, it'll burst out laughing!
待った待った待った！待って、フリフリさせない！フリフリフリフリ…
Wait, wait, wait! Wait, don't make me do the frills!
Frill, frill, frill...
いいね！いえーい！かわいい！いいでしょ！
Nice! Yay! Cute! Isn't it good!
いいでしょ！いいでしょ！ねぇ！なんか楽しいね。え、すごいかわいい！どうしよう、他に誰か、持つ？
Isn't it good! Hey! Somehow it's fun.
Eh, super cute! Anyone else holding?
持ってない人？え、なんか怖い。ドキドキする。
People who aren't holding?
Eh, kind of scary. My heart is pounding.
ラミィも持ちちゃえよ。え？何持つの？どっち？あーーー！いいよ、持って。
Lamy, you hold too. Eh? What do I hold?
Which? Ahhh! It's fine, hold it.
え、次、次はそうだよ。次は、おまるだよ。
Eh, next, next is right.
Next is Omaru.
おっし、じゃあちょっと3人並んでもらって…あー！いいね、かわいい！
Alright, then have the three of you line up...
Ah! Nice, cute!
あ、ちょっと待って、逆がいいわ、逆。逆？逆、逆！
Ah, wait, reverse is better, reverse.
Reverse? Reverse, reverse!
あ、観客席！あーなるほど！逆がいいね。よし、いぇーい！はい、もっとぎゅっとして、ぎゅっとして集まって！
Ah, the audience seats! Ah, I see!
Reverse is better. Yay! Hug closer!
あ、いぇーい！いぇーい！
Ah, yay! Yay!
ねねが…！いぇーい！いいじゃん！ねね大丈夫？
Nene...! Yay! That's good!
Nene, are you okay?
ちょっとね…！いぇーい！天気予報…！ソーシャルディスタンス！ソーシャルディスタンスしてくださーい！
Wait...! Yay! Weather forecast...!
Social distance! Please practice social distancing!
中継に映ってきた人みたいになってる！天気予報とかの裏にいる人だよ！
You look like someone who wandered into a broadcast!
You're in the background of a weather forecast!
いぇーい！いぇーい！はい、かわいいね。じゃあ最後ほら、ポルカ持って…
Yay! Yay! Yes, cute. Well then lastly,
Polka, hold...
ていうかさ、こんなんコメントするほうもさ、かわいいしか言えなくない？
I mean, people commenting on this can only
say it's cute, right?
確かに！かわいい、みんなも。じゃあピンポルカカメラ！
True! Cute, everyone too.
Then Pin-Polka camera!
え、じゃあ獅白牡丹を撮る際は、やっぱさっきの斜め角度がマスターなんですけど。
So when taking Shishiro Botan, as expected,
the diagonal angle is the master class.
ねぇ、じゃあもう一回。はい。あれ、なんかいる？じゃあもう一回。
Hey, then once more. Yes.
Huh, is someone there? Then once more.
こういう感じです。で、えっと、目線こっちださーい！
It's like this. And, um,
eyes this way please!
はーい、はーい！で、えっと、ね、ねねのポーズ、ちょっと、なんか…
Ha-i, ha-i! And, um, Nene's pose,
a bit, like...
いつも通り。これが多分、斜めに一緒に映ってかわいい感じ。
As usual. This is probably cute
with both of us diagonally in frame.
あ、いいじゃん！いいじゃん！はい、いただきました！ありがとうございます！
Ah, that's great! Great!
Yes, got it! Thank you very much!
すごい！フロアだな。ローアングルになっちゃった…！
Amazing! It's the floor.
It became a low angle...!
腹パンみたいになっちゃった！ねね一番かわいいポーズ！
It looks like a stomach punch!
Nene's cutest pose!
ファンサービスポーズ！はい！いぇーい！
Fan service pose! Yes! Yay!
やめないで！なんかさ、ぽるかす、アイドルポーズができなかったから、ねねに教わろうと思ったけどやめたわ。
Don't stop! Polka couldn't do the idol pose,
so I thought about learning from Nene.
ラミィ、アイドルポーズ！
Lamy, idol pose!
美しき獅白も並んで、ちょっとアイドルポーズのお手本見せてて。
The beautiful Shishiro is also lined up,
show us an example of an idol pose.
いいよ、今ねねが真ん中で謎のポーズしてる。え？
Good, now Nene is in the middle
doing a mysterious pose. Eh?
何それ？ねねのポーズは？え、これっぽくじゃん。これっぽい？こういうやつ？
What is that? Nene's pose?
Eh, isn't it like this? Like this?
すごくく、あーかわいいこれ！いただきましたー！
Very much, ah cute this!
Got it!
はい！ありがとー！ありがとー！
Yes! Thank you! Thank you!
わかった。じゃあ、ラミィの何、なんだっけ？ちょっと4人でさ、やりたいな、ちょっと。
I see. Then, Lamy's what was it?
I want the four of us to do it.
じゃあ今のアイドルポーズせっかくだから。ポレカ、ポレカ、ほらこっち真ん中おいで、こっち。
Then let's use the current idol pose.
Come to the center here, this way.
ね？
ne?
はい。
Yeah.
なんかほら、ちょっと、アイドルポーズじゃん、ほら。
So, look, like... idol pose?
えっと、真ん中へんのひとってさ、あれだよね。
Right, right. But the person in the middle...
なんつうか、お前らってさ、なんかこうい感じのがいいんじゃない？
That means you guys, like, look...
ね、ぐー。あ、いいね、いいね。あ、いいね。
Good, good, nice!
あ、でもさ、
Ah, but you know...
よくお前らってこうやってってんじゃん。
Wait, you guys are doing it like this, right?
うん、でも真ん中どこる、そう。
Yeah, but the middle one is like...
え、じゃあ、いこ、いこ。あ、やったー！
Yay!
すごいストレッチしてる今、めっちゃストレッチしてる。
She's stretching right now!
こういう感じ？
Is this good?
あ、いいよ、いいよ！
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah!
よし、よし、よし、よし。
Good, good, good, good!
よし、よし。
Good, good!
折れとる、大丈夫？
Are you okay?
なんでそんな苦しそうの？
Why are you looking so painful?
いや、わからん。
I don't know.
あ、いぇーい。
Yay!
ちょっと何やってんだよ。
Wait, what are you doing?
え、なんだかんだででももうあれじゃね？
Well, anyhow, that's enough, right?
え？
Yeah.
あ、っていうことで、ほら、もうそろそろね。
So, look, let's get down to business.
私たちが集まったら、もうあれでしょうね。
If we get together, you know something will happen.
そうですね。
Yeah, exactly.
この時間は一旦終わりです。
Well, this time is almost up.
え、やったー！楽しかったね。
Yay! Fun!
みんな、あとね、1週間後に迫った！
Everyone, it's just one week away!
そうだよ。
That's right!
いろいろあるでしょ。
There's lots of stuff, right?
あるね、おさらいしていきたいと、
Let's review them!
思います！
Okay!
待って、待って、気付いた？あと1週間後だよ。
Wait, it's already one week from now?
1週間後だよ。
It's one week from now!
というわけで、皆様、
So, everyone,
今週末、3月19日と20日、
this weekend, on March 19th and 20th,
ホロライブ、
the live concert,
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By ヴァイスシュヴァルツ、
hololive 3rd fes. Link Your Wish Supported By Weiss Schwarz,
開催されます！
will be held!
現在、ホロライブ3rd fes.はニコニコ動画で配信チケットを販売中になっております。
Currently, hololive 3rd fes. tickets are on sale as Nico Nico videos!
直前の購入だとちょっとサーバーが混雑しちゃったり、
Buying them right now might mean it gets crowded this month, though.
早め早めに、ご購入をおすすめします。
So, we recommend getting them early.
おすすめします！
We recommend it!
じゃあ次、
Next,
フェスロボメンバーからはDay 1、はい、ねね！
from the fes members, Day 1... Nene?
はい！
Yes!
ポルカ！
Polka?
あれ、私ねねじゃなかった？
Wait, I'm Nene, right?
Day 2！
Day 2!
はい！
Yes!
ラミィ、ボタン！
Lamy Botan!
出演いたします！
They're appearing!
フェスロボメンバー全員のね、まあがんばってる姿が見たい人は通しチケットをおすすめします！
If you want to see the fes members working hard, we recommend the ticket!
今日、もう配信終了後から1ヶ月まで、そのライブの配信終了後から1ヶ月までがアーカイブ見放題なんで、何百回も見られちゃいます。
Today, after the stream ends, up to one month later, you can watch the archive as many times as you want!
よかったね、いっぱい見ようね。
You've gotta watch it!
え、今回のライブ、全編ARってでのライブ演出だったり、生バンドでの演出だったり、
And for this live, there will be AR performances, live bands,
ホロライブイングリッシュやホロライブインドネシアのメンバーも参加して、
hololive English and hololive Indonesia members participating too!
とにかく今までにない挑戦が盛りだくさんとなっております！
It's packed with challenges like never before!
つながってる！
It's amazing!
また、hololive 3rd fes.では、え、今日から、配信リリースされている、
And for hololive 3rd fes., starting today,
ホロライブで新しい全体曲「Prism Melody」がライブ初お披露目されるそうです！
hololive's brand new overall song "Prism Melody" will be unveiled for the first time!
Prism Melody！
Prism Melody!
これだ、これだ！フレー！
This is it!
「Prism Melody」は、はい、ホロライブ3rd fes.のために作られた新曲となっているらしいよ。
"Prism Melody" is a brand new song made specifically for hololive 3rd fes, they say!
お！ねねちゃん映ってない。
Oh! Nene, you're not on the cover?
映って見えて！
I am! Look!
ねね、おれやん！ねねちゃんいるじゃん！
Nene, I'm here! Nene is right there!
な、なんだす、ねねいすに歌わせていただきました！
They let Nene sing it!
どうだった、歌ってみて？
How was it, singing it?
いや、あのね、すごいねキラキラアイドル曲前向きって感じで、
Well, it's a super sparkly, idol-like, positive song,
すごいね、あの、とっても覚えやすくて、たぶんみんなもね、1回聴いたらね、あのサビの「Prism Melody」のところがね、すごい頭に入ってくるんじゃないかなと思います。
and it's super easy to remember, so I think everyone, once you hear it, the chorus of "Prism Melody" will get stuck in your head!
これはね、ライブの前までに覚えてもらって、ライブではね、一緒に盛り上がってもらおうということで、
I hope you listen to it before the live and get hyped together with us!
ペンライトフルタイミングとかね、あるからね。
Penlight, full timing, and stuff...
これはね、ライブで定番曲になるような感じがしたね。
This is gonna be a classic live song, I feel!
あと、この構成がガチで神。最高です。
And the composition is seriously top-tier!
ホロライブの歌うまでがね、
It's before we even sing at the live!
そうなんだよ、すごい！すばら！
That's right! Wonderful!
すばら、ねね、ねねぽ。
Wonderful! Nene!
え、ライブといえば、グッズもあるよね。
And, when it comes to lives, goods are a must-ne!
そう、ホロライブ3rd fes.、ホロライブスーパーエキスポでは、
At hololive 3rd fes. and hololive Super Expo,
ライブTシャツやペンライト、マフラータオルなどのライブの必須グッズがお買い求めいただけます！
live t-shirts, penlights, muffler towels, and other must-have live goods are available!
スペシャルグッズも盛りだくさん！
And there are special goods too!
何々、気になる！
What are those? I'm curious!
それはどこで買えるのっていう購入の詳細、こちらグッズページもあるので、エキスポ3rd fes.のホロライブのこちらホームページ、グッズページに書いてあります。ぜひぜひチェックしてくださいね！
Details on where to buy are on the Good Purchase page, so please check the stay-at-home info!
チェックしてね！
Check it out!
そしてね、今回、うん、ペンライトの
And this time... penlights...
こちらね、ご紹介となります。
Here is the introduction!
ねねは、何色ですか？
Nene, what color are you?
ねね、オレンジ！
Nene, orange!
はい、かわいい！
Yes, cute!
え、あ、赤、レッド！
Um, ah, red, red!
はい、ラミィはライトブルーそして、ししろんは？
Yes, Lamy is light blue, and Shishiron?
ホワイト！
White!
イエーイ！ということで、ここで注目すべき点は
Yay! So, the point to note here is...
見てください、なんか！
Look at this, somehow!
いっぱいあるな。
There are so many.
そう、そうなのよ。みんなね、このライトの色が決まっておりますのでね。
That's right. Everyone's light color is already decided, you know.
ええ、そうなんです！
Yeah, that's right!
え、あ、そっか。い、いなにす がさ、バイオレットでさ
Oh, right. Inanis is violet, and...
ムーナ先輩、パープルなのね。これのちがいね。
Moona-senpai is purple. That's the difference.
なるほど。よく見比べると違うんだよね。ホロライブのメンバーも付いてるのでそのあたりもチェックしてみてください。
I see. If you look closely, they're different. Hololive members are also included, so check that out too.
いいね！いいね！
Nice! Nice!
うれしい、なんか全員のが付いたんだって感じ。ねえ、すごいよ。
I'm happy, it feels like everyone's is attached. Hey, it's amazing.
すごい！
Amazing!
ははは、めずらしい。
Hahaha, rare.
あ、めずらしいよ。ししろのカラー珍しくない？何が？白。白って全然
Oh, it's rare. Isn't Shishiro's color rare? What is? White. White is totally...
そう。アンスノル男女とね、二人並んでるの。ししろの色ってすごい目立つから
That's right. Ans-Noru, a man and a woman, are standing side by side. Shishiro's color stands out so much...
白の色って目立つよな。
White colors really stand out.
ね、だから二人と一緒に振って
Right, so wave together with both of us...
ねねもさ、めっちゃ目立つよね、あの色って。オレンジ振ってほしい。
Nene, that color stands out a lot too. I want you to wave orange.
いいね！ライトブルーも両方持ってお願い！両方持って、両方振ってほしいなと思います。
Nice! Please hold both light blue ones! Hold both and wave both, please.
ということで
With that being said...
以上、もりだくさんの情報をお届けさせていただきました！
We've delivered a ton of information!
あ、あと一週間です。ちょっとね、楽しみに
Ah, it's one more week. Let's look forward to it...
ドキドキだよ。すごいドキドキして。体力気をつけて！
I'm so nervous. My heart is pounding. Take care of your health!
体力気をつけて。どうした？体力大丈夫？
Take care of your stamina. What's wrong? Is your stamina okay?
体力気をつけて。まだあるよ、まだあるよ。
Take care of your stamina. There's still more, there's still more.
意外と痛い。まだあるぞ。
Surprisingly painful. There's still more.
まだあるよ。大事な、大事なことが今からあるんだから。
There's still more. Because there are important things starting now.
そしてこの後はですね、公式ファンクラブでののおまけ配信もあります！
And after this, there's also a bonus stream in the official fan club!
公式ファンクラブでは、コメントのみんなのリクエストなんかもちょっとね、お答えしたいなと思っておりますので、引き続きお楽しみにしてください。
In the official fan club, we'd like to answer some requests from everyone in the comments, so please look forward to it.
じゃあね、せっかくねアイドル衣装でさ、ねぽらぼになっちゃったからさ
Well then, since we're in idol outfits as Nepolabo...
ちょっと、一曲、一曲くらいなんか歌いたいなと
We want to sing something like a song...
この前歌ったばっかじゃん！この前歌ったばっかじゃん！
We just sang it the other day! We just sang it the other day!
えー、この前歌ったばっかじゃん、どうすんの？何の歌歌うの？
Eh, we just sang it the other day, what should we do? What song are we singing?
みんなそう、みんな何の歌を歌うと思いますか？
Everyone, what song do you think we'll sing?
なんかさ、これなるとさとれいって言われるからさ
Because when it's this, people say "Sorei"...
これって言われるとこれってなっちゃうものがあるじゃん。
When you say "this", there's something that becomes "this".
なんただ、わからないな。なんだなんだ？フルクラ。
I don't know. What is it? Full-cla?
いや、この前やったの、そうなん。やったよ。そうなのだよ。
No, we did it the other day, that's right. We did it. That's right.
やってちゃったね。メルクラは、やった？初めてだよね。
We did it. Did we do Mel-cla? It's our first time, right?
あ、そうか。みんなだね、
Ah, is that so? Everyone,
全ての、ホロライブの、全曲の、全体曲の
All of Hololive's, all songs', group songs'...
なんだ？なんだろうね。
What is it? I wonder what it is.
ちょっと、あの水飲むわ。ココアちゃんね。
Wait, I'll drink some water. Cocoa-chan.
ポルカさん、ポルカさん、お水休憩入ります。みんなのみんなの中から歌うからさ
Polka-san, Polka-san, water break. Because we'll sing from everyone's...
お水飲みたい人飲んでね。どこだろ。
If anyone wants to drink water, go ahead. Where is it?
どこ行ったっけ、私のお水。
Where did my water go?
水になっちゃった。ちょっと繋いどいて、その二人で。
It turned into water. Buy some time, you two.
ちょっと繋いんどいて。水飲む。
Buy some time. I'll drink water.
ねねはね、今水飲んだから多分だめだ。
Nene drank water just now, so she's probably no good.
逆にね、逆にダメなタイプだ。イエーイ！イエーイ！イエーイ！
Conversely, she's the type who's bad at it. Yay! Yay! Yay!
あ、みんな戻ってきた。じゃあみんな、初手の位置行って。
Ah, everyone's back. So everyone, go to your initial positions.
初手の位置とか言うな。
Don't call it initial position.
エンジン、エンジンくもな？エンジンくもや。
Engine, engine cloud? Engine cloud.
くむわ。およ。
We'll form it. Oh.
じゃあねねさん、お願いします。お願いします。
Well then, Nene-san, please. Please.
それでは、みんなアイドル衣装でのレポラボの第一歩を踏み出していきましょう！
Well then, let's take the first step of Nepolabo in idol outfits!
レポラボ！ファイヤー！オー！やったー！
Nepolabo! Fire! Oh! Yay!
かったねた 手はぎゅっと離さずに
Holding hands tightly without letting go,
行くよ 行こうよ 夢見る空へ
let's go, let's go to the sky of our dreams!
窓越しに見上げた とても小さい
Gazing out the window at the tiny...
数え切れない奇跡 繰り返し一歩が
Countless miracles, step by step,
きらめきをつないで 星のような笑顔 導いた
connected sparkles, guiding smiles like stars.
道ひらいた 一歩一歩 踏み出した
Opening the path, stepping forward one by one,
その先へ 行こう 夢見る空へ
let's go beyond, toward the dreaming sky.
何度だって みんなの声が 力になる
No matter how many times, everyone's voice becomes my strength.
ステップバイステップ ここで それぞれ 出会ったもの
Step by step, what we each encountered here,
それぞれ 描くもの それぞれの描いた夢
what we each portray, each of our dreamed dreams.
重ねた手は ギュッと離さずに
The hands we stacked, holding on tight without letting go,
一人一人 違う色で 描き出す
painting with our own unique colors one by one.
戸惑うことなく まっすぐに
Moving straight ahead without any hesitation,
振り返ることなく まっすぐに 行くよ
without looking back, going straight ahead!
行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go to the dreaming sky!
笑い合ったことや 月そうにない話題
The times we laughed together, topics that seem endless,
思い出しいっぱいなのに あっと言う間の日々
and though we have so many memories, the days fly by in a flash.
振り返りたくなくて 名前つけて ほうっておく
Not wanting to look back, giving it a name and leaving it be,
どれも全部 大事って 生き切る
living life fully knowing every single bit is precious.
ワンフォーオール みんなのためが力になる
One for all, working for everyone's sake becomes our strength,
オルフォーワン ともに分かち合えるくらい
all for one, enough to share it together.
笑顔が止まらない 想いはふくらんでいく
Smiles won't stop, feelings keep expanding.
重ねた今 ギュッと噛み締めた
The present we stacked, savoring it tightly,
一人一人 違う声で 歌う声は
singing with each of our different voices,
広がる 風を感じながら
as our singing voices spread, feeling the wind,
まっすぐに 行こう 夢見る空へ
going straight ahead to the dreaming sky!
憧れて手のはし 掴み取った
Reaching out for our aspirations, grasping them,
その光が いつのか また誰かの憧れに
that light someday becoming someone else's aspiration,
変わる 繋ぎよ
changing, connecting.
また誰かの憧れに 変わる 繋ぎよ
Changing into someone else's aspiration, connecting us.
奇跡だって証し 続けずっと
Proving it's a miracle, continuing forever,
側にいるよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
staying by your side, let's go to the dreaming sky!
重ねた手は ギュッと離さずに
The hands we stacked, holding on tight without letting go,
一人一人 違う色で 描き出す 時めき
painting with our own unique colors one by one, with excitement.
出会ったすべてに ありがとう 奇跡だって証し 続けずっと
Thank you for everything we encountered, proving it's a miracle, continuing forever,
ずっと側にいるよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
always staying by your side, let's go to the dreaming sky!